Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap401
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Communications and Outreach, 1972-2015
  - News Articles, 1986-2017
    - The Record Op-Ed, 2015
    - The Messenger-Inquirer "Owensboro Judge Calls For Abolition", 2016
    - Wave 3 News Article "Prosecutor and Defense Attorney Weigh in On Wrongfully Convicted Man's Case", 2017
  - Newsletters, 1987-2019
    - Newsletter Material from Don Vish, 2011
    - Newsletters, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters, 2001-2019 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - KCADP Newsletter, No. 12, 1990 June 12
    - KCADP Newsletter, 2000 January 27
    - KCADP Newsletter, Special Legislative Alert, 2000 February 28
    - Article for Newsletter "So this is how it feels…", 2002 March 2
    - Sponsors for IPAct in Congress, Online News Email to KCADP Members, 2002 May 14
    - Tamme Death Press Release, 2002 September 28
    - Eulogy for Eugene Frank Tamme, 2002 October 2
    - Strategy for 2003 News Email to KCADP Members, 2002 December 15
    - Online News Email to KCADP Members "From 1/24 Editorial in Owensboro Messenger-Inquirer", 2003 January 24
    - Murder Victims Family Members Book Signing Announcement for Newsletter, 2003 February 28
    - Eulogy for Paul Stevens, 2003 March 1
    - Online News Email to KCADP Members "NCADP Nashville Conference registration online - EARLY BIRD SAVINGS available!", 2003 May 1
    - George Ryan Report, 2003 June 11
    - Patton and Chandler Statements Regarding Stanford, for newsletter, 2003 June 19
    - The Courier-Journal Vincent E. Senior Obituary, 2003 June 27
    - "So what is the point?", 2003 July 1
    - Library Newsletter, 2003 August 28
    - "Spotlight on Nashville: NCADP Conference Heads to Tennesse", 2003 August 29
    - Email Shared with KCADP Contact List - Kirk Bloodsworth/Death Penalty Book, 2004 August 19
    - Justice PAC Information for Newsletter, 2004 September 2
    - Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation Photograph, 2004 December 12
    - Pat Delahanty with Reporter, 2004 December 12
    - Andrea Rally Group Photo, 2004 December 12
    - Andrea Carl at Rally, 2004 December 12
    - Moore 6th Circuit Case Document, 2005 March 10; 2005 October 4
    - Janice Netherland Obituary, 2005 April 28
    - Peter Reilly Obituary, 2005 May 25
    - Dale Recinella Biography, 2005 June 29
    - Email Messages RE: Annual Meeting in September 2005 Newsletter, 2005 August 15
    - Email Messages RE: Annual Meeting in September 2005 Newsletter, 2005 August 21
    - "The Biblical Truth About America's Death Penalty" Book, 2005 August 29
    - Annual KCADP Meeting Flyer, 2005 October 22
    - "Politics, Religion, and Deaht: Memoir of a Lobbyist" Carl Wedekind Doug Stern Review, 2006 July 9
    - "Politics, Religion, and Deaht: Memoir of a Lobbyist" Carl Wedekind Book Cover, 2006 July 13
    - Bob Schulenberg and Nancy Rowles Photograph, 2006 July 28
    - Andrea Photograph, 2007 January 21
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter "the next big step" Draft Letter for After Newsletter, 2008 May 1
    - KCADP Hosting Ray Krone Announcment for Newsletter, 2011 September 27
    - Beauty Queens at KCADP Booth Photograph, 2011 September 28
    - Ed, Dan, and Steve Group Photograph, 2011 September 28
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 1, 1987 August
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 2, 1987 October
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 3, 1987 December
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 4, 1988 February
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 5, 1988 June
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 6, 1988 October
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 7, 1989 January
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 8, 1989 March
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 8, 1989 March
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 10, 1989 July
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 11, 1989 October
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 13, 1991 August
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 14, 1991 November
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 15, 1992 June
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 16, 1993 June
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 18, 1994 January
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 19, 1994 February
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 20, 1994 February
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 21, 1994 February
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 23, 1997 May
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 24, 1997 November
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 25, 1997 December
    - KCADP Special Legislative Newsletter, 1998 February
    - KCADP Newsletter, 2000 August
    - KCADP Newsletter, 2000 November
    - KCADP Newsletter, Happy Holidays, 2000 December
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 1, 2001 December
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 2, 2002 January
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 2, Extra, 2002 January
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 2, 2002 May
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 3, 2002 July
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 4, 2002 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 1 Issue 5- Extra, 2002 November
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 2 Issue 1, 2002 December
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 2 Issue 2, 2003 March
    - Budget Chart, 2003 April
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 2 Issue 3, 2003 May
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 2 Issue 4, 2003 July
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 2 Issue 5, 2003 September
    - Budget Chart Update 2, 2003 September
    - Budget Chart Update 1, 2003 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 3 Issue 1, 2004 February
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 3 Issue 2, 2004 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 3 Issue 3, 2004 November
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 4 Issue 1, 2005 July
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 4 Issue 2, 2005 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 4 Issue 2, page 3 for web, 2005 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 5 Issue 1, 2006 May
    - Kentucky Capital Dome Photograph, 2006 May
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 5 Issue 2, 2006 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 6 Issue 1, 2007 February
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 6 Issue 2, 2007 May
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 6 Issue 3, 2007 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter, 2008 April
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 7 Issue 2, 2008 July
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 7 Issue 2, 2008 November
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 9 Issue 1, 2009 October
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Vol. 10 Issue 2, 2010 May
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Special State Fair Edition, 2011 July
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter, 2011 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Press Quality, 2012 September
    - Abolition Now! KCADP Newslettter Web Version, 2012 September
    - KCADP Newsletter No. 22, Summer Edition, 1995
    - Opinions by Year and Age Chart for December Newsletter, 1999; 2006
    - Opinions by Education Chart for December Newsletter, 1999; 2006
    - Opinions by Race Chart for December Newsletter, 1999; 2006
    - Draft for Newsletter "Kentuckians Do Not Support Death Penalty For Children", 2002
    - Information for Newsletter, List of Lobbyists for GA, 2002
    - Kentucky Poll Vito Analysis - Data for December Newsletter, 2006
    - "What You Can Do", 2006
    - General Board of Church and Society Statement, 2006
    - Judiciary Committee Members, 2006
    - KY's Capital Realities, 2006
    - Copy for Advertisement "2007 National Weekend of Faith in Action"
    - Newsletter for Ralph Blaze Stay of Execution Thank You, 2008
    - Ray Krone Biography, Final Copy, 2008
    - Ray Krone Photograph, 2008
    - Ray Krone Biography, Draft Copy, 2008
    - Ray Krone Speaking Photograph, 2011
    - History Highlights of Newsletters, 1976-2007
    - Attitudes on Death Penalty Chart for December Newsletter, 1989-2006
    - List of Donors from Newsletter Campaign, 2002 May 18-2002 December 12
    - Copy for Newsletter "NCADP Nashville Conference registration online - EARLY BIRD SAVINGS available!", 2003 October 16-2003 October 19
  - Postcards, 2004-2012
    - Post Card- End of Year Call for Donations, 2004
    - Post Card for Elected Official, 2005
    - Post Card- End of Year Call for Donations, 2006
    - Folded Post Card- "the next big step", 2008
    - Post Card to Govenor, 2012
  - Press Releases, 2003-2015
    - "Death Penalty Coalition Praises Patton" Press Release, 2003 June 19
    - Statement of Rev. Patrick Delahanty on the Occasion of Giving "The Biblical Truth About America's Death Penalty" to Kentucky's Leading Decision Makers, 2005 October 18
    - "KCADP Members to Give Legislators Copies of 'The Biblical Truth about America's Death Penalty'" Press Release, 2005 October 18
    - KCADP Press Release for Release of Carl Wedekind's Book "Politics, Religion, and Death", 2006 September 11
    - "Opposition to Capital Punishment Grows in Kentucky" Press Release, 2006 December 20
    - "Burch: 'End the Death Penalty'" Press Release, 2007 January 5
    - "Death Penalty Coalition Welcomes U.S. Supreme Court Decision to Hear KY Lethal Injection Case" Press Release, 2007 September 25
    - "Catholic Conference of KY Commends Commutation of Death Sentence that Advances a Culture of Life", 2007 December 11
    - "Statement on Behalf of the Associated Press, Kentucky AP Broadcasters, the Kentucky Press Association, the Courier-Journal, the Lexington Herald-Leader and the Kentucky Broadcasters Association Given by Jon L. Fleischaker Regarding Kentucky's Proposed Execution Protocol" Press Release, 2010 January 29
    - "Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Reacts to Illinois Law Abolishing Capital Punishment" Press Release, 2011 March 9
    - "Kentucky Death Penalty Assessment Project Messages for Validators" Draft Press Release, 2011 December 1
    - "Administration of Justice troubling in Kentucky; Report Highlights Flaws in System" Press Release, 2011 December 6
    - "Death Penalty to End in Maryland, 6th State in 6 Years to Abandon It" Press Release, 2013 March 15
    - "Kentucky Family Members of Murder Victims Speak Out Against the Death Penalty in New Booklet", 2013 November 6
    - "Majority of States Not Using the Death Penalty; Fewest Executions in 20 Years" Press Release, 2014 December 18
    - "Pennsylvania Govenor Tom Wolf Declares Moratorium" Press Release, 2015 February 13
    - "Court of Appeals Says NO to Prosecutors" Press Release, 2015 May 22
    - "Victims' Family Members Issue Challenge Grant to Support Repeal of Death Penalty in Kentucky" Press Release, 2015 September 17
    - "Kentucky Conservatives Launch Group Questioning the Death Penalty" Press Release, 2015 October 7
    - Kentucky Department of Public Advocacy Press Release, 2009 January
    - "Polling Results Reflect Continued Trend to Support Use of Life without Parole" Press Release, 2014 October
    - Press Emails for Press Releases, 2014
  - Public News Service Usage Report, 2012-2016
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "An Eyewitness to Execution Brings Her Message to Kentucky", 2012 December 3
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Death Penalty Opponents Sense Momentum, Still Waiting for Action", 2013 February 18
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Momentum for Death to Capital Punishment", 2013 May 15
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Lawmakers Told: 'No Need to Kill'", 2013 November 7
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Lawmakers Told: 'No Need to Kill'", 2013 November 7
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - ""Witness to Innocence" Tour Comes to KY", 2013 November 18
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "An Eyewitness to Execution Brings Her Message to KY", 2013 December 3
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Lawmaker Wants "Arbitrary and Unfair" Death Penalty Abolished", 2014 February 13
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Lawmaker Wants 'Arbitrary and Unfair' Death Penalty Abolished", 2014 February 13
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "KY Lawmakers to Consider, Is Death Penalty Worth Keeping?", 2014 July 30
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "KY Lawmakers to Consider, Is Death Penalty Worth Keeping?", 2014 July 30
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Fun and Serious at the KY State Fair", 2014 August 13
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Freed Death Row Inmate Brings Story to KY", 2014 September 22
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Freed Death Row Inmate Brings Story to KY", 2014 September 22
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "DNA and the Death Penalty in Kentucky", 2014 November 13
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Former Death Row Inmate: "God Bless DNA"", 2014 November 24
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Former Death Row Inmate: "God Bless DNA"", 2014 November 24
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Two KY Lawmakers Want Prosecutors to Put a Price on Death Penalty Cases", 2015 January 28
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Faith and the Death Penalty", 2015 September 8
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Conservatives in Northern Kentucky Form Group to Oppose Death Penalty", 2015 October 13
    - Public News Service Article - "Conservatives in Northern Kentucky Form Group to Oppose Death Penalty", 2015 October 13
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Cost Concerns Drive Conservative Opposition to KY Death Penalty", 2016 February 29
    - Public News Service Media Usage Report - "Hearing Expected On Bill to Abolish Death Penalty in KY", 2016 March 8
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "KY Lawmakers Hear Message of Innocence ", 2014 March
    - Public News Service Alert Via Email - "Historic Lows for Executions Nationwide, Zero Last Six Years in KY ", 2014 December
  - Courier Project
    - "The Death Penalty Has Been A Bad Investment" by David Floyd, Draft, 2015 October 31
    - The Courier-Journal Article "The Death Penalty in Kentucky: A Timeline", 2015 November 8
    - Forum Article "Death Penalty in Kentucky Time for Abolition is Now", 2015 November 8
    - The Courier-Journal Article "Death Penalty has Been Bad Investment For Kentucky", 2015 November 8
    - Courier Journal Opinion Piece by Ben Griffith, 2015
    - "The Death Penalty is an Entirely Avoidable Government Failure", Draft, 2015
    - "The Death Penalty Has Been A Bad Investment" by David Floyd, Final, 2015
    - "The Death Penalty in Kentucky: Time for Abolition is Now" by Allen Ault, 2015
    - "Death Penalty Not the Answer for Many Victims' Family Members" by Ben Griffith, 2015
    - "The Death Penalty is an Entirely Avoidable Government Failure" by Mark Hyden, Final, 2015
    - Timeline of History of Death Penalty in Kentucky, 1972-2015
  - Emails
    - "Illinois: Retiring Justice Calls State Death Penalty Immoral", 2002 September 5
    - Email Message RE: "Utah: 2 Face Possible Firing Squad Executions", 2003 April 28
    - KCADP Email List-Cleaned, 2021 September 15
    - KCADP Email List-Unedited, 2021 September
    - Email Request for Financial Contributions, 2008
- KCADP Corporate Documents, 1965-2022
  This series is arranged into four subseries.
  - Grants
    - Tides Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Rapid Response Grantmaking Request for Proposal, 2003 February 5
    - KCADP Case Statement- The Next Big Step, 2008 January 16
    - KCADP Board Pledges to Date for 3 Year Plan, 2008 January 28
    - Email RE: Strategic Planning for Our Future, 2008 April 28
    - Draft Letter for After Newsletter Volume 1, Issue 1, 2008 May 1
    - KCADP Donor Records, 2008 July 7
    - Letter to Michael Aldridge, 2008 July 11
    - Letter from Michael Aldridge ACLU of Kentucky, 2008 July 16
    - Spreadsheet of Donations, 2008 July 16
    - Letter to Ina B. Bond, 2008 August 11
    - KCADP Job Specification- Director of Public Education & Outreach, 2008 September 9
    - The Loretto Community Special Needs Fund Application Long Range Social Change Projects, 2008 October 10
    - KCADP Grant Information, Unformatted, 2009 August 4
    - Letter of Inquiry for Funders for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2009 August 16
    - KCADP DPMF Grant Letter of Intent, 2011 June 15
    - Budget Template for 2011 Tides DPMF and FADP Joint LOI Application KCADP, 2011 June 15
    - DPMF State Strategies Cover Sheet Template KCADP, 2011 June 15
    - DPMF Grants Committed Chart KCADP, 2011 June 15
    - KCADP DPMF Letter Of Intent, 2011 June 15
    - Media Grant Letter from The Advocacy Fund with DPMF, 2013 November 8
    - KCADP Tides Foundation Completed Grant Application, 2013 July 26
    - DPMF The Advocacy Fund Grant Agreement Letter, 2013 November 8
    - Grant Announcement Letter for Grant # TFR13-02565, 2013 November 8
    - KCADP Report for Grant #TAO13-00089 for $10000, 2014 May 15
    - KCADP Report for Grant #TFR13-02565 for $20000, 2014 May 15
    - KCADP Biographies for 2014 DPMF Grant Application, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Grants Committed Chart, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2012, 2014 August 14
    - Tides Foundation KCADP Organizational Information, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2013, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP 501c3 IRS document, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Narrative for Grant, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Organizational Summary for The Advocacy Fund, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Organizational Summary for Tides Foundation, 2014 August 14
    - Tides Foundation Budget Template KCADP, 2014 August 14
    - KCADP Operating Budget and Actual Year to Date 2014, 2014 August 14
    - Tides Foundation KCADP Budget Template, 2014 August 14
    - Taylor Gray Associates Invoice, 2014 September 30
    - The Advocacy Fund Grant Award Letter, 2014 October 1
    - Tides Foundation Letter of Grad Award for KCADP #TFR14-02593, 2014 October 10
    - KCADP Report for Grant TAO13-00089 for $10000, 2014 November 15
    - KCADP Report for Grant TFR13-02565 for $20000, 2014 November 15
    - KCADP Report for Grant # TFR13-02565 for $20000, 2014 November 15
    - KCADP Grant Award Letter from Tides Foundation, 2016 October 6
    - 8th Amendment Project Grant Proposal, 2020 August 12
    - KCADP Abolition Now! Newsletter Volume 5, Issue 3, 2006 December
    - Abolition Now! Newsletter Volume 1, Issue 1, 2008 April
    - Grant Application Form for Sisters of Charity of Nazareth, 2008 August
    - Copy of Donor List, 2008 August
    - Funders for Alternatives to the Death Penalty Common Letter of Inquiry (LOI) Process, 2009 March
    - Letter of Inquiry for Funders for Alternatives to the Death Penalty for Poll, with abe suggestions, 2009 July
    - Letter of Inquiry for Funders for Alternatives to the Death Penalty for Poll, 2009 July
    - Tides Report from KCADP for $15,000, 2011 August
    - Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Abolition NOW! Organizational Budget, 2003
    - Archdiocese of Louisville Catholic Campaign for Human Development Grant Application, 2008
    - Budget Proposal for Sisters of Loretto Grant Application, 2008
    - Budget for Three-Year, Full-Time KCADP Staffer, 2008
    - Death Penalty Cartoon, black and white, 2008
    - Death Penalty Cartoon, color, 2008
    - Dianne Aprile Contact List, 2008
    - Donors List From Legal Aid, 2008
    - Contacts for "Next Big Step", 2008
    - Envelope For Donations For The "Next Big Step" Campaign, 2008
    - Folded Post Card For The "Next Big Step" Campaign, 2008
    - Job Descriptions for the "Next Big Step", 2008
    - KCADP Case Statement- The Next Big Step, draft 2, 2008
    - KY ACLU Grant Application, 2008
    - Larger Kentucky Progressive Donors, 2008
    - NCADP Group Photograph from DC Trip, 2008
    - "Next Big Step" Case Statement, 2008
    - Potential Donor List, 2008
    - Tides Foundation DPMF State Strategies Application Form Cover Sheet, 2009
    - DPMF State Strategies KCADP Narratives and Bios, 2009
    - DPMF State Strategies Proposal Guidelines, 2009
    - DPMF State Strategies Proposal Guidelines With KCADP Information Added, 2009
    - Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2008 for 2009 Tides Foundation Grant
    - KCADP 2010 Estimated Operating Budget, 2009
    - KCADP 501c3 IRS document, 2009
    - KCADP Biographies for Grants, 2009
    - KCADP DPMF State Strategieis Application Form Cover Sheet, 2009
    - KCADP Other Funding Sources for 2010, 2009
    - KCADP Plans for Future Fundraising, 2009
    - Finding Funding: A Beginner's Guide to Foundation Research 5th Edition Document, 2010
    - Free Online Technical Assistance Seminars for NCADP Affiliates from RESIST!, 2010
    - KCADP 2011 Estimated Operated Budget, 2010
    - KCADP 501c3 IRS document, 2010
    - KCADP 2011 Estimated Cash Flow, Tides Foundation Funds, 2010
    - KCADP Cover Letter for DPMF Grant, 2010
    - KCADP DPMF State Strategieis Application Form Cover Sheet, 2010
    - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2009, 2010
    - KCADP Narratives and Biographies for DPMF Grant, 2010
    - KCADP Need for Funding and Notification, 2010
    - KCADP Other Funding Sources for 2011 Fiscal Year, 2010
    - KCADP Plans for Future Fundraising, 2010
    - A Smattering of Social Justice Funders from RESIST, 2010
    - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year, 2011
    - DPMF Grants Committed Chart, 2012
    - DPMF State Strategies Cover Sheet Template KCADP, 2012
    - DPMF State Strategies Letters of Inquiry for Fall 2012 Funding
    - KCADP Budget Template for 2012 Tides DPMF and FADP Joint LOI Application
    - KCADP Letter of Intent for Tides Foundation Grant, 2012
    - KCADP Letter of Intent for Tides Foundation Grant Draft 2, with edits, 2012
    - KCADP Letter of Intent for Tides Foundation Grant Draft 3, with edits, 2012
    - KCADP Letter of Intent for Tides Foundation Grant Draft 4, with Pat and Kay edits, 2012
    - Tides DPMF – State Strategies Fall 2012 Grants Program Frequently Asked Questions
    - Tides Foundation Grants Committed Chart KCADP, 2012
    - KCADP Final Application with Pat Delahanty Edits, 2012
    - KCADP Financial Statements Spreadsheet, 2012
    - DPMF The Advocacy Fund Organizational Summary Sheet, 2013
    - DPMF The Advocacy Fund Project Budget, 2013
    - DPMF The Advocacy Fund Project Budget Final, 2013
    - DPMF Grants Committed Chart, 2013
    - DPMF State Strategies Letters of Inquiry for Fall 2013 Funding
    - DPMF State Strategies Request for Proposals for Fall 2013 Funding
    - DPMF Tides Foundation Organizational Summary Sheet, 2013
    - KCADP Biographies for Grants, 2013
    - KCADP Draft Without Edits, 2013
    - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2012, 2013
    - KCADP Tides Completed Letters of Inquiry, 2013
    - Tides Foundation Budget for DPMF, 2013
    - Tides DPMF – State Strategies Fall 2013 Grants Program Frequently Asked Questions
    - DPMF State Strategies Request for Proposals for Fall 2014 Funding
    - KCADP Progress Report for TAO14-00052 for $5000, 2014
    - KCADP Progress Report for TRF14-02953 for $5000, 2014
    - Proof of Report Uploaded, 2014
    - Taylor Gray Associates Memorandum of Understanding and Agreement, 2014
    - Tides DPMF – State Strategies Fall 2014 Grants Program Frequently Asked Questions
    - Tides Foundation Capacity Building Grant Application, 2015
    - KCADP Tabling Photograph, 2015
    - Voice Memo Trasncript, 2015
    - 8th Amendment Project Grant Proposal, 2022
    - DPMF Budget Template, 2016
    - KCADP Bank Balance For Grant, 2019
    - KCADP Organizational Project 2021 Estimated Budget, 2020
    - Tides Foundation DPMF For State Strategies Request for Proposals, 2016
    - Tides Foundation KCADP Organizational Information, 2016
    - Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Abolition NOW! Current Fiscal Year Budget, 2002 January-2002 October
    - NCADP Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute Agenda, 2008 August 6-2008 August 8